<objects>
  <object id = "CC_AnalysisMethods_TAYLOR_POLYNOMIAL_OF_DEQ_CANNOT_BE_COMPUTED_1">
    <German>Das Taylorpolynom der Lösung der Differentialgleichung </German>
    <English>The taylor polynomial of the solution of the differential equation </English>
    <Ukrainian>Поліном Тейлора розв'язку диференціального рівняння </Ukrainian>
    <Russian>Полином Тейлора решения дифференциального уравнения </Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_AnalysisMethods_TAYLOR_POLYNOMIAL_OF_DEQ_CANNOT_BE_COMPUTED_2">
    <German>^(</German>
    <English>^(</English>
    <Ukrainian>^(</Ukrainian>
    <Russian>^(</Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_AnalysisMethods_TAYLOR_POLYNOMIAL_OF_DEQ_CANNOT_BE_COMPUTED_3">
    <German>) = </German>
    <English>) = </English>
    <Ukrainian> = </Ukrainian>
    <Russian>) = </Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_AnalysisMethods_TAYLOR_POLYNOMIAL_OF_DEQ_CANNOT_BE_COMPUTED_4">
    <German> kann nicht explizit berechnet werden, da entweder in der Differentialgleichung oder in den Koeffizienten des Taylorpolynoms unbestimmte Integrale auftreten.</German>
    <English> cannot be computed explicitly, since either the differential equation or the coefficients of the taylor polynomial contain indefinite integrals.</English>
    <Ukrainian> не може бути точно обчислено, оскільки або в диференціальному рівнянні або в коєфіцієнтах полінома Тейлора містяться невизначені інтеграли.</Ukrainian>
    <Russian> не может быть точно вычеслен, поскольку либо в дифференциальном уравнении либо в коэффициентах полинома Тейлора содержатся неопределённые интегралы.</Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_AnalysisMethods_TAYLOR_POLYNOMIAL_OF_FUNCTION_CANNOT_BE_COMPUTED_1">
    <German>Das Taylorpolynom der Funktion </German>
    <English>The taylor polynomial of the function </English>
    <Ukrainian>Поліном Тейлора функції </Ukrainian>
    <Russian>Полином Тейлора функции </Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_AnalysisMethods_TAYLOR_POLYNOMIAL_OF_FUNCTION_CANNOT_BE_COMPUTED_2">
    <German> kann nicht explizit berechnet werden, da in den Koeffizienten unbestimmte Integrale auftreten.</German>
    <English> cannot be computed explicitly, since its coefficients contain indefinite integrals.</English>
    <Ukrainian> не може бути точно обчислено, оскільки в коєфіцієнтах містяться невизначені інтеграли.</Ukrainian>
    <Russian> не может быть точно вычеслен, поскольку в коэффициентах содержатся неопределённые интегралы.</Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_AnalysisMethods_TANGENT_SPACE_CANNOT_BE_COMPUTED">
    <German>Die Tangentialebene kann im vorgegebenen Punkt nicht berechnet werden, da die Funktion oder eine ihrer partiellen Ableitungen in diesem Punkt nicht definiert ist.</German>
    <English>The tangent space cannot be computed in the given point, since either the function or one of her partial derivatives is not defined in this point.</English>
    <Ukrainian>Дотичний простір не можна обчислити в даній точці, оскільки функція або одна з часткових похідних не визначена в точці.</Ukrainian>
    <Russian>Касательное пространство невозможно вычислить в данной точке, поскольку функция или одна из частичных производных не определена в точке.</Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_AnalysisMethods_ENTER_A_SMALLER_NUMBER_OF_DIGITS">
    <German>Bitte geben Sie eine kleinere Zahl für die Anzahl der gewünschten Stellen ein.</German>
    <English>Enter a smaller integer for the number of digits.</English>
    <Ukrainian>Вкажіть, будь ласка, менше ціле число для значення кількості розрядів.</Ukrainian>
    <Russian>Укажите, пожалуйста, меньшее целое число для значения количества разрядов.</Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_ArithmeticMethods_SECOND_PARAMETER_IN_MOD_IS_NON_POSITIVE">
    <German>Der 2. Parameter im Operator 'mod' muss positiv sein.</German>
    <English>The 2. parameter in operator 'mod' must be positive.</English>
    <Ukrainian>Другий параметр оператора 'mod' має бути додатним.</Ukrainian>
    <Russian>Второй параметр оператора 'mod' должен быть положительным.</Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_ArithmeticMethods_ROOTS_OF_EVEN_ORDER_DO_NOT_EXIST_1">
    <German>Wurzeln gerader Ordnung können aus </German>
    <English>Roots of even order cannot be taken from </English>
    <Ukrainian>Корені парного степеня не можна брати з </Ukrainian>
    <Russian>Корни четного степеня нельзя брать из </Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_ArithmeticMethods_ROOTS_OF_EVEN_ORDER_DO_NOT_EXIST_2">
    <German> nicht gezogen werden.</German>
    <English>.</English>
    <Ukrainian>.</Ukrainian>
    <Russian>.</Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_NumericalMethods_VECTORS_MUST_HAVE_SAME_DIMENSION">
    <German>Die zu addierenden Vektoren müssen die gleiche Dimension besitzen.</German>
    <English>The vactors to be added must have the same dimension.</English>
    <Ukrainian>Вектори, що додаються, повинні мати однакову розмірнісить.</Ukrainian>
    <Russian>Вектори можно складывать, если у них одинаковая размерность.</Russian>
  </object>
  <object id = "CC_NumericalMethods_UNDEFINED_VALUE">
    <German>Undefinierter Wert.</German>
    <English>Undefined value.</English>
    <Ukrainian>Невизначене значення.</Ukrainian>
    <Russian>Неопределённое значение.</Russian>
  </object>
</objects>